It's week two. Helping this complete
stranger turn $1,000 into $100,000. All
of this learning trading from scratch.
This is officially day one of the
challenge. You can click the sub button.
950 already.
I can't believe you blew the account. We
lost GBP CAD because of [__]
[__] wick out, bro. But you know
what? We're going to deposit the
full,000. So, we're back in the game.
Show the
[__] man. So, right now we are at That
looks good. That looks good.
[Music]
So last week we actually ended up
blowing the account on our first
attempt. On our second attempt we almost
ended up blowing the account but somehow
managed to end off living in profit.
Some margin calls, some mistakes, but we
learned. Now, on week two, our goal is
to not only scale into more positions,
is to end off at $9,000 and on top of
that to make sure that David understands
how to properly be patient and wait for
those right opportunities. With that
being said, let the challenge begin.
What's up, guys? Starting the second
week of the challenge. We're trying to
get it 2,300 to 9,000 this week. Alex
was supposed to be here, but I don't
know where he's at right now.
[Music]
So, I mean, is that like a legit legit
bulletproof vest?
Yeah. You didn't get the memo this week?
We're going to war with the markets,
brother. You're not ready. It's like
that. Like that. Yeah. Give me a second.
Give me a second.
Oh, you have one for me. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
We're going to We're going to [__]
work. Come on. Come on. Oh, it doesn't
fit.
You think this is a game? No. Nice. You
know, if you have two bulletproof vests,
I guess. Oh, brother. Brother. Have you
ever gone to war with the markets,
brother? It's just like you got to like
So like So like that.
Give me Give me a pass, man. Give me a
pass, man. Give me Give me Give me
another one. Give me a pass.
It's week four turning $1,000 to
$100,000. And we're not [__] around
this week. We're going to war. So the
markets is [__]
See that right there? I I see it. You
know what that is? Car. There's a battle
wound. A battle wound. Yeah. We're in
war right now. We're in war with Americ.
We got to got to not back down, brother.
All right. We're protected. This is
right here. This is our stop loss. You
understand? Punch it. Punch you. Not
that hard. Market update, ladies and
gentlemen. Welcome to Sunday. It is
currently midnight on Sunday. Market
right now is at 2,300. We have yet to
take a trade. Why? Because the market
has just opened and we might take
tonight. I'm about to break down the
markets. We are going to be trading for
the week. Make sure you pay attention
because last week we went four for four
on every single market that we
predicted. And this week we have a lot
more than four markets with a lot more
opportunities. I am the captain of this
ship. This is the co- captain. greetings
of the ship and together we're going to
sell this [__] to being a hundred
[__] thousand dollars in profit.
Let's take off.
We're in the same team here, man. All
right, so let's break it down. Euro GBP
is going to be our first pair that we
are interested for the week. So Euro GBP
is going to be the first market that
we're going to be interested for the
week. Right here, we have a very strong
left head and then right shoulder. We
have broken above creating a strong
resistance at this level previously
where we are now here creating
resistance and we're going to expect for
price to come back and have a
retracement of this neckline before
heading to the upside. The 4 hour is
already showing some slowdown at this
area how we've done previously and had
the push to the downside. So right now
we are expecting for the 1 hour in order
for us to enter this counter trend trade
to break retest below to then head to
the downside which will then ultimately
lead us to then us come over here and
have a retest of this neckline along
with the EMA to then head to the upside.
This is a counter trend trade. So once
we make it here then we are actually
interested in buying. Next is going to
be AUD JPY where right now we are
currently bullish. We've had a massive
daily rejection candlestick from this
structure level here. here. And if we go
down to the 4 hour, we can see an
inverted head and shoulders. This
inverted head and shoulders is a very
clear indication that we are rejecting
this area of interest. And I'm waiting
for two things. Either one, for us to
break below these lows. So then we have
a new structure for us to buy or for us
to break above this neckline. And then
once we break above it, we'll wait for a
quick retest. So then we enter the trade
to the upside. Very clean continuation
buys. Next is a very similar trade which
is going to be NZDJPY which we have the
very very very similar daily pin bar
rejection from this area here and we are
below this area of interest. Clearly
whenever we're above we respect it.
Whenever we're below we respect it.
Right now we're below. I'm interested in
buying it once and if we decide to body
closure above it. We have to break it
retest it and then we're going to be
interested to having quick buys right up
to this resistance. The difference
between this and AUDJPY is AUDJPY
actually shifted the structure and we're
bullish and GDJPY is currently bearish.
Euro USD is a very well well swing trade
that is currently loading up. Right now
it's the first time we've successfully
broken above this major level of
resistance since November of 2021. So
it's been nearly 4 years since we've
been above this area. And as of right
now, for the first time in 4 years,
we've broken above it. So, I'm going to
be waiting for a quick retest to then
take this trade to the upside. Next is
going to be our beloved AUD CAD, which
is the trade that we took last week that
actually took the account to $2,300 in
profit, where right now we are extremely
bearish and I'm going to be waiting for
price to have a lower high to then
continue the sells to the downside.
Next, we have USD JPY, which is a bit of
a higher risk trade, but you can see
that it's currently creating a very
strong left head, right shoulder. Right
now, it's creating an additional right
shoulder rejecting from this area of
interest along with the daily EMA. So,
what I'm going to be waiting for is that
the 1 hour has a complete shift of
structure and breaks below creates a
head and shoulders in order for us to
sell. And last and definitely not least
is Euro AUD. Euro AUD looks very similar
to Euro GBP. Left head, right shoulder.
We've had a very strong push to the
upside and we're at this area of
interest right now where I am going to
be waiting for this other head and
shoulders to have a shift structure
which is going to be a counter trend
trade for us to take this trade to the
downside and once and if price makes it
all the way to this area then I'm going
to be interested in taking the buy
positions which are more of the swings
all the way to the upside. So Euro AUD
and Euro GBP are basically identical.
You got that? I got it. You sure? Sure.
You sure? I'm sure. This is a lot of
markets for the week, brother. I see.
But it's kind of like the last week.
Last week was the same thing. The
markets are already fighting back. You
got to be ready. Just you just thought
it and look at that. That's what I'm
saying. The markets are getting
physical. I think it's going to be a
[__] awesome week. Honestly, there's
a lot to go on. A lot of different
markets. All I can say is as of right
now, it is currently 12:25. Well, it's
technically Monday morning. Technically,
Monday morning. We're going to stay up
for London tonight. See what happens.
And forget, see you guys throughout the
night or in the morning. Co-pilot. Set
forget. Morning. So, market update.
Right now, it is currently 9:13 in the
morning where we have currently taken
the trade and we are now at $87,000.
I'm about to finish it.
We're not even We're not even We're not
even [__] close. So, last night we
had some market moves that were pretty
decent, but I believe we are going to
potentially execute a trade right now.
So, let's break it down. So, to start
off, we have Euro AUD where right now we
are currently having that inverted head
and shoulders higher, low, higher, high.
Waiting for that break and retest. Next
we have AUD CAD where we are finally
back up at this area of interest and we
are perfectly retesting this area how we
actually did a couple of years ago. So
right now break retest of this area
perfectly and if I just scoot to the
left you can literally see how I took
this exact same trade right here about 2
years ago. So this July of 2023. So we
had the same break retest sell. So that
can potentially happen once again here
now today. It's happening. the same
thing has happened. Literally this the
exact same price action. So I'm going to
wait for this to have bearish engulfing
candlestick. So I enter USD JPY. It's
currently having the break of the head
and shoulders where right now I'm going
to be waiting for the break of the
neckline, then the retest of it to sell.
AUD JPY, we had the push last night. We
technically missed it, but wasn't really
my most exciting entry. So I'm going to
wait for this to have the pullback.
NDJPY, same exact thing. I had the push,
but I'm going to be waiting for this to
have a little bit of a retracement to
then buy. And Euro GP, no break and
retest to sell. Euro USD, no retest to
then buy. What do you think? Good. We
have, I think, a really good week ahead
of us. What What trade do you like the
most out of all of them? Yeah. ADA. And
I mean, you took it before. You can
expect or expect actually something, you
know, out of it. Last time I took it
down here, it was a loss, but when I
took it 2 years ago, it was a fat win.
Super fat win. So, I think we're going
to have this. I mean, I would [__]
hope so. So, I think with this week, the
goal was 9,000, right? Yeah. I think
with this week, we can we can be $1,000
over. Yeah. To like 10,000. 10,000.
[__] It's I mean, look at look at the
amount of pairs. It's a really good
week, I will say. Yeah.
David, how does it feel like to be week
two in the challenge? Awesome.
Interesting. Enthusiasm. What are you
most excited for this week? Getting to
9K. Actually, surpassing 9K. So, what
were some of the things you learned last
week? I mean last week we started now
actually doing the actual live trading
and I mean I was doing the whole course
thing and I mean of course you learned a
lot of the technicals and everything but
now seeing it live how it moves and how
it behaves is way way more type of
learning. Do you feel confident this
week being the co-pilot that majority of
decisions are going to be based off of
my person? Yes. Yeah, for sure. 100%. Of
course. I've been studying. I've been
seeing the last week how it was. So I
think I'm ready to take the leap. And
apart from the whole trading thing,
how's your fitness goal going? How much
are you weighing right now? Good. Good.
I mean, I don't know if you remember,
but when Knight came to the house, I was
at 236. Now I'm at 225. Still 25 lbs
more to go. But hey, progress. It's just
week two, right? Week two. And I already
lost 11. I think in the remaining weeks
I can No, I think No, I'm 100% that I'm
going to draw the other 25 remaining.
Well, I'm going to let you study now.
Let you do your thing. First of all, let
me see if you can keep your studying. I
check scratches this. Huh? Um, that's
Look, I have a lot, but I doubt anybody
gonna understand this except my doctors
in the chat. If I have doctors, they
will for sure understand it. Nobody
else. All right, boys. Straight update.
Right now, it is currently 1:06 in the
afternoon, and today has consisted of
just looking, literally doing nothing.
Yeah, but let me show you. The markets
have done stuff, but we haven't executed
on it. Just to show you the account is
the exact same spot. No new positions.
AUD CAD right now. We are currently
having a larger pullback from this area
than we expected. We're still going to
be waiting for sales sometime tonight in
London. Next is going to be USD JPY,
which earlier this morning we broke
below very strongly from this area, but
we managed to retest above and not
actually close below it. So that's why
you always have to wait for the
candlestick to close. The daily time
frame looks like a very strong
rejection, which is going to close in 4
hours. We're going to wait for that Euro
AUD. We have indeed broken below this
left head right shoulder and I'm going
to be waiting for a retest to then sell.
This is probably going to be my number
one trade and I'm most likely going to
be taking this trade tonight. If you
notice last time we had a strong bearish
engulfing from this area. We had a
retest and then sold and we actually
entered that position and made a [__]
ton of money right here. Very clean
break retest. And as you can tell right
here, we're literally getting the exact
same thing. Game break retest. NZDJPY
basically hit the takerit, never pulled
back. AUDJPY on the way to the takerit,
never pulled back. And Euro GBP is
having a very clean reaction from this
resistance, creating another potential
daily dogee, which we're going to be
waiting for the exact same thing as Euro
AUD break retest to then. So, let's get
a [__] workout in. Touch it. Touch
it. Touch it.
Ah. Oh, yeah. You'll get a workout in.
You know what I'm saying? Can you Can
you do that? I can, but it's not going
to do as good as you. Why you looking at
me like that? It's kind of like what?
I'm looking dead in your eye. You're the
one looking under.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, we have
now made it to Mexico after a long drive
across the border. See,
we're going to teach this [__]
how to drift right now. So, do you know
Yeah. Do Do you know how to drift? I I I
think I barely even remember how to
drive manual. So, you've driven a manual
before? Yeah, but I mean you in Colia
like you know like the whole time that I
was in my uncles didn't have a car.
Yeah. I want to say I barely remember
how to you understand the basic clutch
in first, second, third, fourth. Okay.
So, this is the same thing, but you're
just going to pop the clutch. You're
going to turn the steering wheel 80°
leave it in first and then you're going
to counter steer when you're going the
other way. I see it. Yeah. The [__] All
right. So, what we're going to do right
now is I'm going to teach you how to
drift. I'm going to teach you how to do
a basic donut. When we pull up to the
spot, you have about 2 minutes of solid
donuts and then we got to book it before
the cops come or one of us go to jail.
And then we're going to go to the other
spot and then me and Seas are going to
do some tangent drifting to show you how
professional this is. Okay. All right.
And when the cops show up, the rock
paper scissors, right? So we can see who
goes to jail, right? Cuz No, no, no.
We're going to leave before that.
Anything past 2 minutes, we'll go to
jail. So yeah, I've timed 2 minutes to
learn how to drift. 100%. Don't worry,
I'm going to be timing. You'll be fine.
So I'm going to pull up hot.
Yeah.
[Music]
[Applause]
Punching. Go. Wait. One more.
Fire hurt.
[Music]
Heat.
day to show some
[Music]
mission after mission.
And we're back. We made it out alive. We
made it out well. Safe and sound. We
successfully blew up the tires in the
Miatas as that was a great drifting day,
gentlemen. Without that, it would have
not been a proper drifting day.
Honestly, it was a little bit mid
because you did not get much practice
in. How did you feel? I I did though.
Like I did. I thought I was not going to
be able to just like even start it.
Yeah. You almost stopped. I'm not going
to lie. But no, no, like what I'm saying
like I had to get the the thing the
clutch, but hey, I started and after
that you told me pop it, bump it, bump
it, and I just [__] Yeah. No, not
we're going to actually put you to test
for real cuz you're going to go in front
and then I'm going to follow you. What?
But market update. Right now it is
currently 9:29 in the evening and as of
right now we are yet to take any new
trades into the account. We have missed
some opportunities but we haven't
executed one and we might execute one in
the next 30 minutes. Let me break it
down. So starting off the markets with
Euro AUD. Currently we are creating a
very very strong left head right
shoulder. The daily time frame is
clearly having a reaction from this
level. Last time we were here, we had a
massive daily bearish engulfing
candlestick which we entered on the next
day on the wick pullback retest and then
we caught the cells. We made a lot of
money here a while ago. And if you
notice, it's the exact same thing
happening here. Massive daily bearish
engulfing and right now it's potentially
creating that wick pullback. 4hour time
frame head and shoulders. 1 hour time
frame we're already seeing some type of
a slowdown along with an engulfing here.
So I'm going to wait for a little bit
more confirmation to enter this trade.
But this is exactly where I'm going to
look to enter this trade. My stop loss
will probably somewhere around here. My
take profit somewhere around here. Next
is going to be AUD CAD where currently
we had a very strong daily pullback up
into the neckline of this area. And
right now we're potentially having a
reaction to then sell. The 4hour time
frame has had a beautiful evening star
formation, but I can't sell at this low.
So I'm going to be waiting for price to
kind of give me a little bit more of a
pullback, give me what it can
potentially look like a double top or
even just a little bit more of a
retracement. So the risk-to-reward makes
sense cuz right here the risk-to-reward
will not make sense. So the higher up
the better but I am actively looking to
enter this trade. Next is USD JPY. So
earlier we were looking to sell at the
break and retest of this. But we did not
get that proper break. So we never sold.
This is why you have to be extremely
patient and follow your trading plan so
you don't enter an unnecessary loss like
this. This next trade is now this
perfect higher higher low higher high.
We're going to wait for a break and
retest to then sell which is exactly
what we waited for here. here. But if
you notice, wasn't a proper break and on
that retest, we got no bearish
confirmations. Very easy trade to avoid
a loss on. Next and most definitely not
least is going to be Euro GBP where we
have created a double daily dogee at
this resistance level. Last time we were
here, we created multiple daily dogeis
before heading to the downside. And I
can anticipate the exact same thing
could happen here. 4hour time frame is
creating a massive double top, but I
only want to sell once we can properly
break and retest below this area to have
a proper trade. NGD JPY and the AUDJPY
have hit the take profit. So, we have
missed those trades. No biggie. We got
plenty of opportunities currently
loading up as we speak. So, this right
here, I'm going to wait for it to close
in the next 27 minutes in order for me
to make a decision if I'm going to enter
this trade right now. So, right now, we
have a beautiful evening star bearish
engulfing candlestick confirmation
happening and I'm going to decide if I
enter this trade. I just got the most
craziest text. I know just texting me
right now. That's crazy. That's crazy.
All right, let's see what we get into
tonight. We're gonna wait to see if we
take this trade and said I forget. All
right, guys. Market update. It is
currently midnight. So, we've been here
for about like 30 minutes. We're at the
music video. Well, Anol was hitting me
up cuz he wanted to use this couple
cars. This car for the Yeah, two of
these cars for the music video. He's
doing like a kind of like an underground
vibe, whatever. He wanted me to do
donuts in the Miata in it.
Straight update. 1 a.m. 1 a.m. Right now
we are up 1,600 bucks. Say what? Oh, you
haven't seen it. 1,600 bucks. So, I
think we're about to get started right
now. We've been here an hour, right? We
pulled up at 12. We picked up by
midnight around Yeah. I mean, the trade
was at 12. So, yeah. Right now, the Euro
UD is having a very strong push to the
downside. AUD CAD is having a double top
and USD JPY has officially broken it,
but not exactly what I want. So, I'm
going to continue to hold this position.
So, you guys ask me how do I stay up for
London? You should like this. We We
shoot music videos. That's how we stay
up. You're going to be in the music
video. Yeah, I know. I know. They asked
for me, the J kid. Yeah.
[Music]
Trade update 4:16 in the [__]
morning. Trade is looking at me. I don't
even know where David is. I think David
is sleeping behind the bed or something.
I don't even know where he is. Trade
update. Right now, trade is looking very
strong. Right now we're up about 2500 on
the account. We are currently
having a rejection from here, but I'm
not looking to close Euro AUD for now.
USD JPY had a very clean break and we
are now retesting to sell. I'm just
going to continue holding Euro AUD.
Right now it's
4:00 in the morning, so I don't forget.
I'm going to take a nap in here. They're
almost done supposedly. Check back in.
Market update. Last night we um did a
whole lot of nothing for a long time.
Market update. Right now it's 1:35 in
the afternoon. So we got here around
6:00 in the morning yesterday, 7:00 in
the morning, and we woke up probably
like an hour ago. We are a little bit in
draw down right now. So the market is
having a retracement back into the area.
So yesterday we were up about 2500 and
almost $3,000 I saw at one point and now
we're back at break again. So let me
show you. So yesterday we had a perfect
reaction from this left head right
shoulder perfect break retest push and
then throughout the whole entire London
session what we were looking at last
night. Whereas this basically trickle
into profit right here. But then
basically towards the end of London
session and the beginning of New York or
like in the middle ending of London
session price now is starting to have a
retracement. So, right now we are
probably in the worst time to be holding
this trade right now at this area
because the market is going to be
closing in about 3 and 1/2 hours. So,
the spread is about to get ridiculous.
The spread alone can blow us and
literally hit our stop loss. So, I'm
going to make a decision in the next 30
45 minutes to see if we close this
position here at a $400 loss and then we
just potentially re-enter it in London,
right? Cuz we don't want to get the
account blown. This is like this is a
major key thing that I've seen happen
very consistently. A lot of people blow
their accounts or lose a trade when the
market closes because the spread goes it
literally gets like 7 to 15 times more
of what it would normally be. So I can
take you out. So I don't know. I don't
want to make a decision just yet because
this candlestick in the next 23 minutes
can literally just completely have a
push to the downside. Another thing is
this right here. By the way, I am
dropping so much free fire game on these
videos. If you guys don't take
advantage, you guys are going to
completely miss out. I am literally
teaching you guys and David behind the
camera or off the camera so much
valuable [__] that you like I just don't
ever talk about. Like look at this,
right? The decision that's going to help
me make if I'm going to hold this trade
or not is this right here. So if you
notice break retest, look at the time
down here 123 whatever, right? And I'm
like all right, let me see what happened
last time price was down here. Well, I
took a break and a retest and then a
sell. And then on that retracement, it
comes right back to my break even at
what time? 123
14. And then it has the push. So all I'm
doing is looking left. I'm seeing the
same pattern. And then I'm looking at
the same time. Same [__] should happen
again. It should. Right. Right. Mhm.
Right. Mhm. But it's not.
Almost. Go. You get give it a shot.
Wait. The mouse. S. Give it. Give it a
punch. Wait. Wait.
Entertainment today. The people.
Ah, bro. Punch it, man. Again. Yeah,
punch it like you mean it. Okay, hold
on. Hold on. Oh, wow. Punch it now. It's
going to [__]
Oh,
yo. Yo, that's perfectly fine.
Oh. Yo, no way. Did Did the screen
break,
bro? Did you break the screen?
You broke the screen. Well, we're
officially down a screen. Thanks, man.
Thanks, brother. You're You're not
welcome. We're going to we're going to
we're going to take this off of the top
of the 100,000 that we're going to make
here. Thank you. Now, we have to make
104,000, brother. That's fine. So, we're
going to basically make a decision here
in the next 30 minutes to see if we
decide to hold or close. Then, we have
AUD CAD where we're going to be waiting
for a pullback to sell USD JPY. So far,
nothing. And you're a GVP. Nothing.
Market update 144. We will check back in
later. What the [__] happened, man? Why
are you asking me the questions? It
captain the co-pilot. Yeah. Whatever I
do, you're supposed to verify and make
sure I'm doing right. Right. So, I'm
going to ask myself and I'm going to ask
you. Okay. I don't know what happened,
man. Oh, I don't know.
Enter the trade. Enter the trade again
right now. Fix whatever we did wrong.
Fix it. Fix it. Fix it.
didn't do [__] [__] man. We got Margin
called right now once again. Yeah. Let
Let it out, bro. Let it
Thanks. Do you want We can We can sell
this to to get another account if maybe.
Ladies and gentlemen, we got margin
called once again. So, the account is
currently right now sitting at $1,300.
Balance. What letter is that? I thought
it was an L. Imagine that. No, that
would have been I mean, actually an L
for learning lesson. That's a seven
backwards. Learning lesson. You've been
trading very hard. I think you deserve
this. I got you a little gift.
Is that a [__] double L? We got
margin card. Right now, the account is
currently at the balance of,346.
equity of about $900. So today's trade,
we got margin called at $1,000 at a
loss. And I believe we're going to blow
the account right now, honestly. So
price has come back into this area. We
have basically created the exact same
rejection from this structure point
177500.
And we're just going to wait for the
4hour time frame to see if we're going
to close above in the next hour and 16
minutes and uh see if we can reject it.
be rejected. I'll enter again. If not,
we will set and forget. USD JPY nothing
U AUD CAD massive push to the downside.
We're going to be waiting for some types
of retracement to then for us to enter
the cell. Everything aside from that was
F. Dude, we could have closed at 5,000
in profit. So, why didn't we close
yesterday? We were up 2500. We We were
at 5,000. That comes up 5,000. Let me
explain, bro. Let me explain. Let me
explain. So, our take profit is where we
close the trade, right? because this
trade had the potential to reach that
area. You don't want to just look at the
money. You got to look at it for the
trade. So, yes, I get it. We could have
possibly been up 5,000 at this point
right here. But like that means that if
we would have executed this trade and we
would have closed there, we would have
only been up a 1 to 1.5, which makes no
sense. We always close our trade at a
minimum of a 1 to2 risk-to-reward
despite whatever you're doing. You get
me? So if you if you're looking at it
for the money, obviously it made more
sense to take to close the trade out
there. But it just risk-to-reward wise,
it makes more sense to close it always
at a minimum of one to that's the math
on how we're going to complete this
challenge. So what happen if we get
margin call now like again like on this
new on this position, do it again. Start
over. Do it all over again. And if this
trade goes back into profit now, we're
just going to enter new positions and
continue to go. So pretty much for the
rest of the day now, I'm going to get
the [__] out of this office cuz I'm like
raging. And we're going to come back
tonight for London session. Check back
in.
I get it. Probably like, "What the [__]
What happened? Are we good? Uh, this
suck." Yeah, it sucks. All I have to say
is [__] happens and we are all good. and
I don't want to talk about anything else
about it. [__] happens.
Move on from it and talk about it maybe
later. But for now, I really don't want
to talk about it. Let's just continue
back with the challenge and let's
pretend and let's just put that behind
us. So, we got to forget again. I know.
Same thing. I know. I know. Martin Cole,
welcome. You seen You seen the patterns
here, right? Yeah. You're kind of
looking like me now, bro. You think I'm
starting to look like you? Yeah. You're
starting to look like your hair is kind
of getting like mine. You know, you're
kind of like you're getting stressed
like me, you know? That's good. I think
that's good, right? You're getting into
the vibe. Yeah. But yeah, we got Margin
called earlier today and right now the
trade is in profit. So like this is what
I'm talking about. Like we technically
did not lose the trade. We just got
margin. Like we're right about the
direction, right about the entry, right
about the stop loss. Since we're just
overexposing our account, we basically
got whipped out by margin, not by the
actual trade. Yeah. And it like but this
is a common thing to happen like in what
we're doing like account flips or in
general as a trading. Yeah. If you're
overexposing your account, you're very
prone to getting margin call. Mhm. And
you still being right about the trade,
but just because the trade goes into a
bit more draw down than you anticipated
when you went to go risk on the trade,
you can just take a loss. But yeah, it's
it's a normal thing to happen when you
are doing higher risk trades like this.
You get me? But when you're actually
trading properly, risking 2, three,
four, 5% margin calls, this type of
stuff never happens, right? Okay. So,
let's break it down. Right now, we have
Euro AUD where we are currently having a
perfect retest of this area right now.
And this is the trade that we took
earlier. We were in a little bit of
profit and then we had a major
retracement back into this area. This is
where we essentially got the margin
call. And if you notice, our stop loss
was placed above these highs
strategically. In the event it did have
this retracement. Once again, since
we're in a high lever trade, we don't
have to make it all the way up to this
high in order for us to take the loss.
We could just take the loss because
we're overexposed in here. So, we're
still right about the trade because it
never hit our stop loss, but we took a
loss because we overexposed ourselves.
I'm going to be waiting for this
candlestick to close in the next what
does that say 42 minutes for me to make
a decision if I'm going to enter this
trade just because right now it looks
good but not exactly what I need or
maybe I just wait for an extra 30 or
maybe for I don't know like an extra 11
minutes for this candlestick to close or
close a little bit more bearish I just
need I need a little bit more in order
for me to enter this trade that's Euro
AUD AUD CAD we've had an accumulation at
this area and the daily time frame close
with a strong daily pin bar rejection
And then we've had a massive push to the
upside now. Basically creating an almost
equal wick where on the 2hour 4hour it
looks like it's creating a triple top or
it could be creating a left head right
shoulder. So I'm going to wait for a
bearish candlestick to then have the
strong push to the downside. USD JPY we
never had the shift of structure so we
never took the trade. Euro GBP we never
had the shift of structure so we never
took the trade. And uh these trades were
already gone. EuroUSD. I'm very
interested in it for it to have a
reaction from this area here to then
buy. So, right now, we're going to be
waiting for some type of bullish
confirmations around this area to then
buy cuz right now we're up. Hold on. So,
what would be like the best entry to
have in this type of challenges like
that you did on the 100 mil? Mhm. Like
entry signals enter a trade. I mean, it
really depends on the type of trade that
you're going to take. So, if you're
going to take a scalp trade, you want to
have a rejection from whatever area that
you're going to be entering and you
enter on the rejection and then that
engulfing is basically your whole entire
move. But if you are having an intraday
or a swing trade, you want to have the
rejection happen, the engulfing happen,
and then that's your confirmation to
enter the trade. Difference between both
entry signals is one of them use the
rejection as your entry. You're
anticipating the engulfing push to be
your profit. The other is you're waiting
for the engulfing push to happen. So
then there you enter the trade and
that's your confirmation. So it really
depends on the type of trade that you're
going to take. There's no real best
entry confirmation. It just depends the
type of trade that you're going to take.
Okay. Okay. So technically what we're
doing now is since we're waiting for
that engulfing on Euro AUD on AUD CAD,
we are literally waiting for
intraday/swing trade. And also I mean
I've been seeing like a lot of head and
shoulders. For example, look maybe over
there we're going to form another one.
Yeah. Is that like your favorite pattern
or like the one that you follow the
most? Yeah, head and shoulders for me is
the perfect reversal pattern and it's
what consists of a perfect shift of
structure and it basically creating a
perfect entry with a perfect stop loss.
Yeah, the head and shoulders just
happens to be a pattern, but it's also
an accumulation of a perfect shift of
structure. So, yeah, for me it's the
best on top of double tops, double
bottoms, everything. We're going to
continue to trade that and as of right
now, I think every trade we've taken is
off of Head and Shoulders. With that
being said, market update 12:30 in the
morning. About to enter London session
real soon. We will see you guys in the
morning. Well, it's Yeah, in in a bit
more morning. Yeah, actually. Yeah,
because it's already like today. Yeah,
technically. So, see you guys soon.
Market update, bro. It is currently
11:00 in the morning. So, we've been out
for a little bit, but we just been doing
like other videos. So, right now, we
reentered a position on Euro AUD and
it's looking pretty decent. This is
[__] [__] bro, because the TR we
didn't lose the trade. Let Let me just
show you real quick, right? We did not
lose this trade right here. Like this
this trade that we lost right here. We
literally just got margin caught. It's
[__] This is the actual trade
technically because we never got margin
called, right? I mean, yeah, we never
got margin caught. Price never hit our
stop loss. We took a loss just because
we overlever and we got margin called,
but the trade is still right. We were
never wrong about the direction. And
last night after the 4hour closure with
this massive bear bearish engulfing
candlestick, I was not going to enter
all the way down here because I always
anticipate the wick pullback. We got the
wick pullback and then the 30 minute on
this pullback. We got our perfect
engulfing after retesting the structure
level and then having the rejection from
the EMA. So that right there is this
entry right here that we then scaled
into and I believe this is going to
continue having strong push to the
downside. The only thing I don't like
about this is that we have fundamentals
today. that we have some CAD news, some
USD news, but then we have some
Australian news at 9:30. These news at
9:30 can have a big either add-on to
this push to the downside or it can
completely reverse everything. If you
notice, we are literally taking the same
trade here, break, retest, sell, as we
are right here. Break, retest, sell.
According to my calculations, we have
about another literally like the exact
same couple 4hour candlesticks left.
Have the exact same couple 4hour
candlesticks left. We should have the
news fundamentals do this, not the other
way, right? But we never really ever
know. So, we're going to wait for this
to have that right there. Now that I
think about it, majority of the trades
that we have taken that we've been like
winning have been in the morning. Like,
is that normal? What do you mean more?
Or like like Yeah. 4 in the morning, 3
in the morning. Is that normal? Uh, I
say it's normal for the market that
we're trading. I guess I I say it's
normal in general. Yeah. Like it's not
that we only take trades in New York. We
only take trades in London. It just
really depends on the trade, but taking
trades at that time is normal. Yes. But
like I I don't always stay up for that,
you know, like sometimes trades don't
give me the opportunity in New York and
then I can tell that it's going to set
it up for London. Sometimes I can tell
nothing's going to happen in London and
then it sets it up in New York. But it's
not like I'm always up. I'm only up when
I have to be. So always like this like
the best session to trade on. The best
time zone to trade on. Yeah, it really
depends on again so many different
factors. Depends the day, depends the
market. But if I were to pick a session
to take a trade on, it would always be
London because if you take a trade on
London, it has the whole entire push on
London and then it has the continuation
push in New York. If you take a trade in
New York, then it just kind of dies out
after New York, then it picks back up.
So I would really, like, for example,
right now this trade, they're in London,
it had the push. The rest of New York
should just continue to have it a push.
Then the other session, it just
trickles. Then London session kicks in
with then New York. Okay? or it can
literally just
and then we [__] up again. So market
update right now we are currently at
1,900 about 3200 in profit. It's it's
funny like yesterday like like at this
time was not a good morning and I mean
now so for now all we're going to do is
set and forget the ADA last night around
this area it did not give us the
engulfing candlestick so we did not take
the trade. What price did is that we
then had the continuation push to the
upside. We never got a rejection here.
So, we never took the trade. Euro GBP,
no Breita, no breaking retas, no sell.
Euro USD, it is currently cooking up a
perfect buy. I just want to wait for the
daily time frame to close to see if I
can use that in my favor. And last but
not least, GBPD. We're just going to
buck it around for now. Set forget.
Trade update. Right now, we're sitting
at around Oh, it's looking good. Decent
about $2,500 in profit. Balance is 38.
So, if we would have not lost the first
trade, don't even tell me that. Yeah.
Like, if we do the sum of all this [__]
we shouldn't be losing. We'd be up so
much money right now. Like, not double,
but like close to double. No, we'd
probably be up almost double. Like, we
didn't lose the last margin call. Yeah,
that's what I'm saying. We would just
continue to hold. Yeah, we would be up
total of eight lots. Yeah, we'd be up a
little bit more. But whatever. Market
update. Currently, we are moving in our
direction very well.
Euro AUD is having very strong daily
bearish engulfing momentum. I'm going to
keep holding to my takeprofit area right
now. The 4hour time frames had a very
clean push. 2 hour 1 hour having a
strong push. AUD CAD no signs of bearish
movements. USD JPY still waiting for
break and retest to sell. Euro GBP no
break and retest to sell and every
single the market is kind of just not
doing anything right now. So, time for
You're going to go hit the gym now,
right? I'm going to stay out here to
think of how the margin call affected us
and how it affected our journey and how
it minimize our profits to get there
faster and how I'm Okay, we're just
going to settle for good. See you guys.
Market update. It is currently midnight
right now. We are up about $2,000 in the
account.
So, we're slowly cooking. This trade can
potentially be our last trade for the
week kind of. I don't know. I'm going to
definitely So, you said you're saying
that that trade can take us to the
9,000. Um, I don't know, man. I have to
see how the next hour candlestick
closer, the next 30 minutes. Based off
of that, I'm going to then determine if
I close the trade or not. And if I close
the trade, then we enter another trade.
I was going to ask you if we're going to
just close that one and enter another
position or just I mean it really
depends. All right, so let me show you
guys. Right here we have Euro AUD and
we've had a massive push from this
neckline to the downside. Beautiful
continuation shift to the downside.
Beautiful bearish push. Even we had the
news have the retracement retested this
area and is still having the push. But
you guys have to remember like this is a
major counter trend trade. We did the
countertrend trade up into this area
because we have the left head right
shoulder. We're retesting the neckline
and the structure where we can
potentially now have the higher high
push. Yes, we took the exact same trade,
the break, the retest, and then the
sell. But the market at this point had
this area to be the first place where it
can have the retest before having the
push to the upside. Here, this is the
first area where this market can have
the retest before having the push to the
upside. So, we can't be greedy and
expect for this market just to continue
going down just because we predicted
this one move right here. And this right
here is our takeprofit, which is always
a minimum of a one to two. And we
technically hit that. I just stretch it
out a little bit and put a little bit
low. So, I'm just going to wait to see
if it closes how I want it to. I might
hold a little bit more, but I might just
close and then enter buys to the upside.
I don't know. I need to see how price
action plays out for me to make a
decision here. AUD CAD on the daily time
frame. We actually pulled back all the
way to our entry where we were last
week. massive bullish push retracement
back into this area which I did not
expect that especially after the weekly
time frame having a massive weekly
bearish engulfing candlestick with such
a large wick. The 4hour time frame is
indeed bullish on this retracement.
Lower high lower lower higher highs and
higher lows all the way up into this
area. But I might be interested in
sells. Just going to be waiting for this
to see how it rejects around this area.
Lendon sensation tonight is going to be
crazy. USD JPY potential sells still
waiting for the break and retest below
this neckline to then sell. That is yet
to happen. Once that does, I'm going to
be very interested for sells. Euro GBP,
we did not have a break and retest below
this area. So, we never sold. Trade just
kept going to the upside. NZDPY on the
other hand is very, very clean. We are
retesting back this inverted head and
shoulders, which is what I wanted at the
beginning of the week to buy. We had the
push for the buy, missed it. Now, we can
potentially enter the buys around this
area. now that it is retesting this area
to potentially create another rejection
off of this area of interest that is
very well respected. AUDJPY is not quite
there yet, so not super interested. And
EuroUSD, we are very interested in it,
especially since we are having a
reaction from this area right here. This
is going to be a very clean level of
resistance that can potentially be used
as support or we're going to buy this
trade to the upside. So, I'm going to be
waiting for this to enter the trade. And
last but not least, GBP NGD has had the
retest of this area where then it is now
selling. Well, can potentially sell, but
it had the retest exactly how we
anticipated. We're going to be looking
for sales.
That was a lot of talking. Yeah, it's
looking really nice, though. I mean,
there's a lot of opportunities. That's a
double-edged sword, right? Yeah, cuz you
could be tempted by the opportunities
that are out there. We want like the the
mo the most important thing right now is
to preserve our capital, right? We want
to make sure we can close this as high
as we possibly can. Right now, we're
about 1,800 bucks. Once we close this as
high as we can, we can then decide if
we're going to enter another trade. And
how do you how long do you think it's
going to take for the other ones to take
to get to the take profit zone? Uh, I
mean, usually it could take anywhere
from I mean, we've had trades go from
like 4 hours to then like four or five
days. So, an average would be anywhere
from like one to two days more or less.
Like there there's never like a concrete
timeline on a trade, okay? As long it
could take. And after we finish with
this trade, like either if we close it
or it takes profit or we're gonna risk
again 100% on the next trade, probably.
Yeah. Okay. I mean, it'll depend on the
trade. It depends on how much profit we
close on this one. The goal for the week
is 9,000 and we're at 3,000 if we close
right now. So, technically, we would
need another one to two on the trade.
Maybe we risk like 50 60%. It really
would depend on better. As of right now,
this market update for London session at
midnight. We'll check back in in the
morning.
Bro, why is this not focusing on that?
Is it not [__] focusing? No. Why?
Why? I guess I guess Are the profits not
[__] focusing? What about now? It's
still not Oh. Oh, there we go. There we
got it.
What is going on, ladies and gentlemen?
Market update. It is currently 6:06 in
the morning as you guys can see to the
top right hand corner. So, I am just
recording this on Zoom right now because
everybody's asleep and honestly, I don't
really want to like have the guys just
be up sitting here next to me for no
reason. Like, I've been literally like I
fell asleep like this with my head down
all night um for like the last 2 three
hours. And uh I decided to do the market
update now instead of wait till the
morning. So, I'm just going to screen
share and show you guys where things
are. Let me show you guys. We executed
or we closed out on the sells exactly
how I anticipated. Basically, if we
waited for that 4hour candlestick to
have that closure, we were then going to
enter the buys and then we entered the
buys, right? So, just wanted to show you
guys. Yeah, going to break it down right
now on Euro EUD. So, 4hour time frame
came into this area. I'm already seeing
how it's going to close with a bullish
pin bar. I'm already seeing the 1 hour
have the 1 hour engulfing. And as that's
happening, I said boom, we got to close
it. Close the trade. And then I
basically broke down earlier how I could
anticipate this trade to have a push to
the upside. We are taking a counter
trend trade in this move right here.
Price could have a reaction from the
structure point from the neckline of
this head and shoulders and that's
exactly what happened. Very impulsive
trade. I basically anticipated for
London session to do exactly what it's
doing right now. And I'm going to look
to get out honestly simply because I
don't like this area that we're in right
now. Obviously, whenever we're below it,
we're selling. Not saying that I don't
believe we're going to continue to push
up, but I think we are going to have a
retracement before we push up. And
truthfully, I'm tired of seeing my
trades going to loads of profit and then
not close it there. Like, if I would
have closed this trade all the way at
the bottom here where I should have, I
was just being extra greedy. My account
would have probably been up like a 5K. I
would have risked more on this position.
I'd probably be up like 15k right now.
So, I'm I'm lowkey getting kind of tired
of constantly just overstretching the
trade. And it's crazy because when I'm
supposed to, it doesn't work. Or not
that it doesn't work, but when I'm
supposed to just I don't do it. And then
it has the crazy, you know, 1 to 10
risk-to-reward. And when I do do it,
then what ends up happening is that the
trade actually has a complete, you know,
reversal. So, this trade right here, we
had the engulfing, went to the trade,
and waited for a little bit. I think it
was 15 minute. We got a little bit of a
push above the structure level right
here. And yeah, we're ready for that.
Right now, it is currently 6:00 in the
morning. You guys can see live price
moving down here at 6:15 in the morning.
And all I'm going to continue to do
right now is to hold. I might close this
position in the next 15 30 minutes. I'm
just waiting for I don't even know if I
want to wait for this candlestick to
close because I believe New York session
is just going to have the retracement
honestly. So, I might just close now. I
don't know. I'm going to wait for this
15 candlestick to close. So, the close
is engulfing or some bearish momentum,
I'm just going to completely close it
and then just let the trade do its
thing. Yeah, pretty boring explanation,
not going to lie. But market update,
6:10 in the morning. I'm literally
seeing the sun come up barely on any
sleep. We're up uh about 4 grand right
now and we're going to continue to set
forget, but I might close very soon. All
right, I'm back. It's funny cuz I'm
literally talking to myself and you can
see how it's daytime now. Like, I'm
literally just sitting here and I'm
watching the sun come up and I haven't
[__] slept anything. It's 6:22 in the
morning. So, what, like 15, 20 minutes
from the last update? Last update was at
$4,000. And I'm literally seeing my
profits just like trickle away. I'm
literally seeing the technicals. And I
am completely understanding that this is
going to reject this area exactly how I
said. And that this market is literally
going to have now a higher low to then
have any higher high. I should lock in
these profits before. So, I'm going to
close this live right now here with you
guys. So, it's literally rejecting
exactly how I anticipated. I just want
to close this live with you guys. I want
to do this live with you guys here. Bulk
operations
close out positions.
[__] man. [__] We didn't stay at
$6,000 in profit, bro. By [__]
dollar, bro. [__] I need to get some
rest. 6:00 in the morning. I haven't
slept anything. I will check back with
you guys in a little bit. But for now,
this market is having a reversal. If it
has another pull back into this area,
I'm then going to be interested in
buying AUD CAD. I was interested in
selling, but really didn't like it as
much as Euro AUD. USD JPY, no breaking
retest, no seller GBP, nothing. And ZD
JPY, nothing right now. Hasn't gave me a
strong engulfing as a confirmation. Euro
USD. No strong confirmation to enter
this trade just yet. I want to wait for
this daily to close even though the 4
hour looks good. GBP NZD did not stop
here. And that is it ladies and
gentlemen. We'll check back in later.
Good morning. Morning everybody.
Morning. Last night I was in the I was
in the war room by myself and we got
[__] done. Yes.
Now honestly, bro, like I get it. So
last night everybody was fried, right?
cuz we we haven't slept for like 2 days.
And on top of that, I know you're on the
diet. The diet's kind of [__] me up.
We're starting the fasting already.
Yeah, bro. I'm telling you, like you
could see the physical change in your
face, dude. Like, if we could pop up
some clips of like his fluffy face when
you pulled up, bro. Now you look better.
You look like a man now, bro. Like, you
look like a look like a dude. You get
it? Feeling testosterone.
Well, it's too much testosterone this
close, right? Like there's a little
market update. I mean, you guys already
know what's happened last night. We
close out the position at 5,999.
And let me show you guys where we are
right now. Just to show you guys like,
bro, literally people inside of my
community catching these trades all of
the time. This guy said, "EA buys,
thanks for the update." There's always
people that are delayed and don't see
stuff. But look, I let show you guys
what it looks like on the Telegram. So,
literally yesterday, last night, I sent
it, right? So, look. All right, guys.
Market update. Market update. So, it is
pre-lending session right now. The
account is currently sitting at about
3,200
in equity. So, what a [__] week so
far, right? It's been a week already.
It's it's it's been a week and I think
it's going to be another long night,
right? So, quick market update on Euro
AUD.
As of right now, we have had a very
strong push following yesterday's London
session. So, our last update was very
precise. We entered off of this retest
continuation push, and I believe this
was just another lower high to then
continue pushing to the downside. I
don't dislike entries here. It is
extremely high risk and I don't
recommend it at all. I believe that this
right here is going to potentially have
a reaction from this structure point.
So, have to keep that in mind because
the daily time frame could be creating
this potential higher low retesting this
neckline around this area to then
continue pushing to the upside. We have
to remember we are taking a counter
trend trade and we have to know where
our limit is and where we get out. We
can't just think just because we caught
a single move right here, we're going to
catch the whole entire thing. So, keep
in mind that from this area right here,
we can especially buy, we can also have
some sell. Just be on the lookout for
it. I'm going to keep holding it just
for a little bit longer before I make my
decision on what I'm going to do next.
You guys can literally see that we
called it yesterday to perfection. And
after this retracement, we closed here.
We entered and then it had the push. You
got literally like me being tired last
night made me close this out and not
continue to hold. If I would to continue
to hold, not only would I not be up only
5,999,
I probably up a little bit over like
like 10 10. Yeah, 10. Wow. Yeah, easily
$10,000. A CAD continued to have a push.
Honestly, not even that interested in
this. And then continuing from this, USD
JPY, no breaking retest, no sell. Euro
GBP, nothing. NZD JPY is currently
cooking up a potential entry. Just got
to wait for this daily time frame to
close because I don't like how that is
right now. And I don't want to buy again
such a massive big red candle. I believe
it's got to cook up a little bit before
that. Euro USD, as of right now, it's
cooking up as well. I don't think this
trade is going to be ready this week
because I don't want to buy after a
bearish candlestick. If you have a dogee
like this, you anticipate a continuation
push from that. you don't anticipate for
it to have a bearish push to the
downside. And last but not least is
GBPND back up into this resistance area
exactly how it was last week where we
could potentially enter the exact same
trade literally again right here. So,
we're going to be waiting for some price
action to enter this trade.
That being said, that's the market.
Yeah. So, I I fell asleep probably like
at 7:00 in the morning and I probably
woke up like at 11:00. And now that I
was not here last night, I mean, let me
ask you something. Why we actually like
what did it show you that you wanted to
like get on the buy on your AUD last
night? Uh so basically we had a I mean
this trade is bullish, right? It's lower
low, lower high, lower low, higher high,
higher low, higher high, higher low,
higher high, inverted head and
shoulders. We have the neckline. We
currently retested the neckline and then
when we go down to the 4 hour, you see
how price basically bottomed out and it
created a rejection. We have our
engulfing candlestick. And then when we
go, we have the engulfing and morning
star formation. And when we go down to
the 1 hour, this is like the secret
sauce and a lot of people know which is
going to be like the timing of it. This
happened right at the beginning of
London session. This is a perfect break
retest. The news event had a massive
rejection along with the EMA from this
area. It then had a bearish push to the
downside that should have continued
going down with the impulsiveness of
London and it did not. So since it
completely engulfed all of that, I
expect London session to continue having
this push to the upside. Now towards the
end of the London session is where I
anticipated for New York to have the
retracement but it actually just kept
pushing it up to the upside. So I
entered this trade just purely because
of volume and one because it's the
actual trade I should be taking. I
should be taking the trade following the
trend and because of this price action
right here. But then what why didn't we
keep holding? because I believed that
this was a strong level of resistance
right around here and then that it was
going to have a retracement right last
time whenever we're below it we reject
and technically we were below it when we
were there and I was seeing rejection
candlestick so I decided to just be a
little bit more conservative and more
cautious yeah cuz if like the last thing
I want to do is continue to have trades
go into profit and they all come back a
break even like this literally happened
to us with every single trade this trade
right here that we were in when we were
all the way down here was in profit
probably like almost $3,000
We closed for $1,000 in profit on that
trade right there. So, with that being
said, set and forget. We'll see you guys
later.
[Music]
I'll give you a hundred bucks right now
if you could dunk at that height. I
cannot cannot do that at all. What about
like couple inches lower? Maybe. Maybe.
You want to try? Yeah, let's try it out.
All right, we have there at half an
inch. Stay hanging. Yeah. You sure? It's
not my rim. cuz I can.
Oh, what was that? I'm trying.
Bro, all that hype for nothing, bro.
No,
not today, man.
So, that's the only way you could dunk,
huh? All right, boys. Market update. We
look a little messed up because we're
playing some basketball right now. Late
night session. It is currently 1:00 in
the morning. Uh, no trades in the
account right now. Everything is exactly
the same. But we got some anticipation
for London tonight. I'm going to be on
the more conservative side simply
because it is the last session of the
week. The week and we want to make sure
that just because we want to hit like a
dollar goal. We're not forcing something
that of course lose more than for being
greedy. Exactly. All right. So, let me
break it down. Right. AUD CAD having the
perfect pullback up into this area again
to be interested in sells. Right now the
2hour one hour is having what looks to
be like a head and shoulders daily time
frame close as a clean daily bearish
candle. Might come back and create a
rejection from that EMA but I'm not
going to be taking a trade here cuz I
want to see how the weekly closes. Euro
AUD right now we are having a
continuation push really nothing that I
can do here. USD JPY no breaking retest
no sell your GBP nothing. NZDPY. So, we
waited for the daily time frame to
close. We had a perfect closure at this
area of interest. The 4hour time frame
had a massive bullish engulfing
candlestick. We even came back, created
a perfect higher low retracement with a
1 hour engulfing, and now we're having
the push. Honestly, I did not enter cuz
we were playing basketball. So, I wasn't
even I missed on the trade. We're
[__] playing basketball. Charge it to
the game. It's okay. So, this trade is
pushing to the upside. If we have a
little bit of a retracement, I might
consider entering it. I don't want to
chase it. If we have a little higher
low, I might enter, but chasing it is
definitely not the play. I don't really
want to enter late on it. Euro USD, same
exact thing. We had a beautiful
engulfing from here. The daily time
frame closed with a beautiful daily
bullish pin bar. This is why you have to
wait for the price action to like play
out. But I'm not interested in entering
right now just because we're already so
far from where I would have entered the
trade. We're at 30 pips in profit and my
risk-to-reward would completely change
if I would enter up here. So, I'm not
interested in this one either. We
technically missed it. We got a little
pullback. I might enter it. And lastly
is GBP NZD. So we're having the exact
same rejection from here how we did from
this area here. So I might be interested
in selling here especially after the 1
hour had the 1 hour double top 1 hour
bearish engulfing. And on top of that,
it's technically had a shifted
structure. This is the higher low. Shift
the structure. We pull back. We could
sell. I'm going to wait for this 1 hour
time frame for this 4 hour time frame
over here to close in 11 minutes so we
can see if we're going to determine if
we're going to enter this trade or not.
So, so far it's looking like GBPND.
Honestly, I I don't think it's worth it.
Do you think it's like ideal actually
like you have all the experience? Do you
think it's ideal to enter the trade?
Honestly, if the trade makes sense, it
makes sense, right? Like just because we
were up a certain amount of money
doesn't mean that the market is fully
aware of that and it doesn't mean that
what we did previously has direct
correlation to our next results. our
last trade have no direct correlation to
our next trade. So we could have won 10
trades in a row doesn't mean the next
one's a win. We could have lost 10
one's a loss or a win or whatever. So
just because we had a great week doesn't
mean that the next trade is going to
make it a bad week or even better week.
So we got to just treat the trade for
what it is and in the next 7 minutes
we're going to be able to determine if
it is. So yeah, I would I would honestly
say is it worth it? It's always worth it
if it makes sense. Okay. And now if if
we do enter, are we going to risk 100%
again? Probably
honestly not really. I think that that
would be stupid, you know, cuz if we're
to be like Tuesday, fine, sure,
whatever. But I think since it's like
the last couple of hours, we should risk
like 20 30%. If it's already Friday, I
imagine. Yeah, I know. 100%. Yeah, it's
basically Yeah, I agree. So, it depends
on the trade. Okay. So, we'll check back
in in the morning. Morning.
I look uh I look fried, bro. Um I think
this is the first night in four nights
in a row that I've slept a full night's
sleep. Yeah, I got my full 5 hours of
sleep, bro. Insane. Like, you know how
good I feel? That's crazy. You know when
they say that when people sleep a lot,
they grow. You feel like you grow. How
much? Oh, I'm taller than you right now.
No. No. Yo, is it real for real? Yeah.
Okay. Like I I believe in myself, bro. I
believe in myself so much that last
night we literally avoided the [__]
because of me sleeping right now. Like,
thank God. Thank God. Market update.
Right now it is currently midday so we
still haven't taken any new positions in
the markets but we avoided many losses
missed out on one trade no big deal
right so AUD CAD last night
hypothetically let's say we would have
taken this trade down here at London
session price would have came up took
out a stop loss and then continued to go
to the downside truthfully I would have
not placed such a big stop loss on this
market just because the risk-to-reward
would have never made sense I would have
not expected for this market to have
this whole move in the last couple of
hours of the session. So the market is
setting up per like this is the most
insane alleyoop we are getting for next
week right here. Like this is literally
Dwayne Wade passing it up to LeBron.
LeBron coming behind the back and just
boom. LeBron's still in the Miami Heat,
right? Of course. Yeah. Yeah. Right. I
think he just won MVP like last season.
That's what I'm talking about, bro. This
right here is the same play happening
right here. We're about to get MVP
because of this layup alleyoop. We're
[__] getting AUD CAT. Next trade is
going to be well technically this trade
we just avoided this wick out. Next
trade is Euro AED. Never in a million
years would I have anticipated this
mammoth of a candlestick after having
major rejections from this neckline at
the head and shoulders and this
resistance level. So we we anticipated
the sell and then we anticipated the buy
because this was a counter trend trade
right here. And then this is the trade
continuation. I exited around here
because I expected for the daily time
frame to create a small retracement. So
then next week it has the push. They
said, "Yeah, [__] that. We're just going
to continue having the push and that's
what we're looking like right now.
Massive bullish pin bar to the upside.
Daily just barely any retracement. It
kept going. This sucked. If we would
have kept holding this, we'd be up so
much more money right now. But it is
what it is. Uh USD JPY, no break, no
retas, no sell. Euro GBP. I'm good. NGD
JPY. We had to wait for this daily time
frame to close as a strong pin bar and
then for us to anticipate for this trade
to have a reaction. So after this
bullish engulfing last night that we had
here which we would have entered here
price actually came back gave us a
little bit more confirmation but
basically what I said I don't expect
this to have the move right into the
last couple of hours of the week and
Euro USD is the exact same thing after
the trade had this bullish pin bar we
had a retracement literally an hour ago
and this retracement went back to our
entry point perfectly and rejected head
to the upside there's no way in hell
that this has that red full-blown
candlestick and I say [__] yeah let me
enter you you know, it's just not going
to happen. So, avoided this trade or
missed out on it somewhat. And then
lastly is GBPNZD. GBPND is a perfect
example of if something doesn't work
two, three times, don't try and do it
again, right? Because this like after a
strong rejection of an area like this
and we come back and we reject it and we
come back again like this means that
this move right here was just not strong
enough. So, why is this going to do it
again? Right? I was just a little bit
speculative about it. It was just not
clean last couple hours of the session.
Alex G personally myself of 2021 2022
even 2023 maybe even last year maybe I
would have lost this trade 100%. Like I
would have taken this position because I
would have just think okay you know what
it's happened multiple times it's going
to happen again. And I I say that a lot
that's true but it's how is it doing it
again? And this did it again by having a
m like literally massive daily bullish
engulfing candlestick. There's no
confirmation rejection here. This had
the exact same daily bullish engulfing
candlestick, but then it had a daily
rejection candlestick after the move.
And even after that, we still had a
liquidity grab before the actual move.
So yes, it I say it all the time that if
it happens again, it should happen
again. But it's how it happens again,
should it happen again. So my decision-
making around trades like this has saved
me a lot in the last couple of months.
Now with with I mean with how the market
has been, you know, like the last couple
of weeks, you think it's going to keep
going like that? Like when it comes to
volatility? Um, I don't know if I don't
know if it's going to be like that cuz
usually out of the month or historically
with the Biden markets, there's four
weeks in the month. Obviously, there's
two good weeks and then there's two slow
weeks. We've already had the two good
weeks. So, following that theory, we
should def like technically have then
two bad weeks going. Yeah, not bad
weeks. Yeah, slow weeks, right? So, I
can anticipate next week to be a bit
slower. I'm just going to be a little
bit more conservative on the trades,
meaning that I'm going to wait for them
to have a little bit more confirmations
before entering them. Having that in
mind, right, the public challenge ends
in two weeks. Do you think we do you
think we're going to be able to get to
the goal to the final goal now knowing
that we have like two maybe slow weeks?
Yeah. Oh, no. We're going to get to the
goal no matter what. I'm talking about
in just the two weeks. Um I don't know
about two weeks. I don't know. That
means that next week we would have to
turn the 6,000 to 18,000. Then the week
after that, the 18,000 to 100,000. Yeah,
there would be no way. We' probably need
like three more weeks. Or if next week
we somehow turn the 6,000 to like
25,000, then the next week we could turn
the 25 to 100. I mean, you know, [__]
it. You know, I it really depends on
next week. If next week goes really
well, we'll be good. Listen, maybe maybe
it's as as volatile. Maybe this is a
historical month. Yeah. I mean, maybe
that'd be awesome, dude. I would love
that to happen, you know? But yeah,
that's that's pretty much it for right
now. It's currently noon and uh see what
we do for the rest of the day and how
the market closes. All right, boys. Time
to get smoke. So, the way we're going to
play today is if you get hit once,
that's not out. Like, you only get out
when you quit. You can get shot four
times and if you want to get out, you
get out. But if not, you don't. Sound
like a fair deal? Not a fair deal. We'll
see about that.
I heard they checking for me. No one
checking on me. So, I had to go run up a
check. I got the message on me and no
flexing on me. My attorney will call and
collect. Blessings on blessings for me.
successes only made them envious. They
got upset. I had to put all their egos
in check. I went the money to pride
respect and I heard you know so and so
you not a threat cuz I really know so
and so. They like my family so they
pretend that they cool till they busted
your [__] chest. I'm getting
good at my flow like on my check. They
see the number all of my haters feel one
of two ways. Really upset they show some
it for the week boys. Week two in the
books. Week three next week our goal is
to take 6,000. Hold on. Hold on. Hold
on. Let's Let's make sure we're not
[__] lying to anybody here. to make
sure we're not being fugazy right now.
5,9992
cents to hit 12,000 or 18,000 would be
the final. That being said, ladies and
gentlemen, hit that like and subscribe
button. If you want to see the behind
the scenes with the whole entire journey
with David, join the 17 down below so
you can see how this happened in real
time. That being said, thank you for
watching. I got smoked, they got smoked,
and we're going to smoke the market next
week. Set it for you have anything. He
said he said we got to drop some
information like the last video. Drop
drop some [__] Drop some [__] like like
like one video. Off the dome. Off the
dome. Off the dome. Go. Go. Get the
lighting in his face. Get the golden
hour. Go. Say something. What is off the
dome? Like off your head. Off your head.
No, but with the sun in your face, bro.
So it's more majestic. 3 2 1 go. Frozy
processes.
What the [__] was that, bro? Listen, I
didn't have time to think. No, no, no,
no. I have to say something
inspirational. You have like 15, 20
seconds. Three.
3 2 1 go. I have nothing to say. Hold
on. I got like I got it. Even in times
of war, how we are now, there's a way on
how to make peace, whether before,
during, or after. That's exactly what
we're doing here. You see how none of
that made sense and it still sounded
motivational?
Like some inspirational songs I forget.
[Music]